<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Certifications on Cr0w&#39;s Place</title>
    <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/tags/certifications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Certifications on Cr0w&#39;s Place</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Thomas Sermpinis</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 16:56:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cr0wtom.github.io/tags/certifications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Certifications - Offensive Security Certified Expert</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/certifications-osce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/certifications-osce/</guid>
      <description>OSCEs have expert-level penetration testing skills. They have proven that they can craft their own exploits, execute attacks to compromise systems, and gain administrative access. The intense 48-hour exam also demonstrates that OSCEs have an above-average degree of persistence, determination, and ability to perform under pressure and can think outside the box to determine innovative ways of penetrating internal networks. An OSCE also has familiarity with more advanced protections like ASLR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certifications - Offensive Security Certified Professional</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/certifications-oscp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/certifications-oscp/</guid>
      <description>Offensive Security Certified Professional (OSCP) is an ethical hacking certification offered by Offensive Security that teaches penetration testing methodologies and the use of the tools included with the Kali Linux distribution (successor of BackTrack). The OSCP is a hands-on penetration testing certification, requiring holders to successfully attack and penetrate various live machines in a safe lab environment.
An OSCP is able to research a network, identify vulnerabilities and successfully execute attacks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
