<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitHub on Cr0w&#39;s Place</title>
    <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/tags/github/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitHub on Cr0w&#39;s Place</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Thomas Sermpinis</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 16:56:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cr0wtom.github.io/tags/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Mi AI Button Remapper</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-miai_remap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-miai_remap/</guid>
      <description>I created a Magisk module that allows you to remap the dedicated Mi AI hardware button of the Xiaomi Mi 9 and Mi Mix 3 to any one of 15 user-selectable functions.
The mod is availavle in the Magisk store, and you can directly download it from there.
Magisk Project Link
Project Link
XDA-Developers Thread
Some blog threads that talked about my work:
Thread 1
Thread 2
Thread 3
Thread 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Xiaomi Mi9 Stereo Mod</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-mi9_stereo_mod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-mi9_stereo_mod/</guid>
      <description>With this Magisk mod you can hear sound for both the speaker and the earpiece in stereo mod. Original module by acervenky for Mi 8, modified for Mix 3 by Nukeclears and for the Mi 9 by me.
The mod is availavle in the Magisk store, and you can directly download it from there.
Magisk Project Link
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Cross-chain Transactions</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-cross-chain_transaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-cross-chain_transaction/</guid>
      <description>This repo contains possible implementations for cross chain transactions platforms, that need support for multiple cryptocurrencies. Due to this fact several ways can be used to implement cross chain transactions. Some of the methods are described bellow, with PoC code in the folders of this repo.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Ethereum Voting</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-ethereum_voting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-ethereum_voting/</guid>
      <description>This is a project developed during my blockchain research in the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
This project includes decentralized voting capabilities to support the decentralized addition of new organizations in the final Plastic Twist network (Horizon 2020 European Project). It uses the blockchain technology to exploit its capabilities and especially the Ethereum Blockchain, to be easily applicable to the initial system created by Almerys.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - New Organization Blockchain Voting Platform</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-hyperledger-voting-chaincode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-hyperledger-voting-chaincode/</guid>
      <description>This is a project developed during my blockchain research in the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
This project includes decentralized voting capabilities to support the decentralized addition of new organizations in the final Plastic Twist network (Horizon 2020 European Project). It uses the blockchain technology to exploit its capabilities and the Hyperledger Fabric framework, to be easily applicable to the initial system created by Almerys.
For more information, technical specifications and installation instructions head to the repo wiki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - New Organization Blockchain Voting Platform</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-hyperledger_channel_configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-hyperledger_channel_configuration/</guid>
      <description>This is a project developed during my blockchain research in the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Hyperledger voting for new peer join in channel. This repo includes the setup and information needed to vote and join of a new peer in a hyperledger privet network channel.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - DeTRACT Smart Contract</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-sc/</guid>
      <description>SSL/TLS Certificate Authority Replacement through Ethereum Smart Contracts. The project was developed alongside the academic paper based on my Master&amp;rsquo;s Thesis for Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - DeTRACT with Bitcoin Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-t_bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-t_bitcoin/</guid>
      <description>SSL/TLS Certificate Authority Replacement through the Bitcoin Blockchain. The project was developed alongside the academic paper based on my Master&amp;rsquo;s Thesis for Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - DeTRACT with Ethereum Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-t_ethereum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-t_ethereum/</guid>
      <description>SSL/TLS Certificate Authority Replacement through the Ethereum Blockchain. The project was developed alongside the academic paper based on my Master&amp;rsquo;s Thesis for Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Mi Notebook Pro Mods</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-mi_notebook_pro_mods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-mi_notebook_pro_mods/</guid>
      <description>Mi Notebook Pro by Xiaomi is a 15inch laptop which was widely adopted because of its good price/performance ratio. This made it a huge success and created a big community of hackers wanting to fix some minor issues that the laptop had, alongside adding new capabilities, like natevelly running MacOS.
I created a repo including all the available mods, and additional stuff I created for this device.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - OSCP - PWK Repository</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-oscp-pwk-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-oscp-pwk-repo/</guid>
      <description>During my time at the PWK labs and for my OSCP preparation, I gathered a big amount of useful stuff that I want to share and make available to the community. With a huge amount of respect to the Offensive Security team, I will not disclose anything about the labs and the exam, but I will give general information and study lines for the young padawans out there who want to TRY HARDER!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
