<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academic on Cr0w&#39;s Place</title>
    <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/tags/academic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Academic on Cr0w&#39;s Place</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Thomas Sermpinis</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 16:56:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cr0wtom.github.io/tags/academic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Academic - DeTRACT a decentralized, transparent, immutable and open PKI certificate framework</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/detract-a-decentralized-transparent-immutable-and-open-pki-certificate-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/detract-a-decentralized-transparent-immutable-and-open-pki-certificate-framework/</guid>
      <description>The academic paper based on my masters thesis and research made during my work with the OSwinds research team of the Aristotle Unicersity of Thessaloniki got published in Springers&#39; Internationa Journal of Information Security by the name &amp;ldquo;DeTRACT a decentralized, transparent, immutable and open PKI certificate framework&amp;rdquo;.
Thanks to the team, George Vlahavas, Konstantinos Karasavvas &amp;amp; Athena Vakali.
Abstract Public key infrastructure (PKI) is widely used over the Internet to secure and to encrypt communication among parties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Cross-chain Transactions</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-cross-chain_transaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-cross-chain_transaction/</guid>
      <description>This repo contains possible implementations for cross chain transactions platforms, that need support for multiple cryptocurrencies. Due to this fact several ways can be used to implement cross chain transactions. Some of the methods are described bellow, with PoC code in the folders of this repo.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - Ethereum Voting</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-ethereum_voting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-ethereum_voting/</guid>
      <description>This is a project developed during my blockchain research in the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
This project includes decentralized voting capabilities to support the decentralized addition of new organizations in the final Plastic Twist network (Horizon 2020 European Project). It uses the blockchain technology to exploit its capabilities and especially the Ethereum Blockchain, to be easily applicable to the initial system created by Almerys.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - New Organization Blockchain Voting Platform</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-hyperledger-voting-chaincode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-hyperledger-voting-chaincode/</guid>
      <description>This is a project developed during my blockchain research in the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
This project includes decentralized voting capabilities to support the decentralized addition of new organizations in the final Plastic Twist network (Horizon 2020 European Project). It uses the blockchain technology to exploit its capabilities and the Hyperledger Fabric framework, to be easily applicable to the initial system created by Almerys.
For more information, technical specifications and installation instructions head to the repo wiki.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - New Organization Blockchain Voting Platform</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-hyperledger_channel_configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-hyperledger_channel_configuration/</guid>
      <description>This is a project developed during my blockchain research in the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Hyperledger voting for new peer join in channel. This repo includes the setup and information needed to vote and join of a new peer in a hyperledger privet network channel.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - DeTRACT Smart Contract</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-sc/</guid>
      <description>SSL/TLS Certificate Authority Replacement through Ethereum Smart Contracts. The project was developed alongside the academic paper based on my Master&amp;rsquo;s Thesis for Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - DeTRACT with Bitcoin Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-t_bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-t_bitcoin/</guid>
      <description>SSL/TLS Certificate Authority Replacement through the Bitcoin Blockchain. The project was developed alongside the academic paper based on my Master&amp;rsquo;s Thesis for Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub - DeTRACT with Ethereum Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-t_ethereum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/github-detract-t_ethereum/</guid>
      <description>SSL/TLS Certificate Authority Replacement through the Ethereum Blockchain. The project was developed alongside the academic paper based on my Master&amp;rsquo;s Thesis for Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Project Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks - Consensus Algorithms (Greek)</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/talks-consensus-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/talks-consensus-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>Presentation at the &amp;ldquo;Bitcoin &amp;amp; Blockchain Tech Meetup (Thessaloniki)&amp;rdquo; taking place at Thessaloniki.
Presentation Video
Meetup Link
Slides</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic - Traceability Decentralization in Supply Chain Management Using Blockchain Technologies</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/traceability-decentralization-in-supply-chain-management-using-blockchain-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/traceability-decentralization-in-supply-chain-management-using-blockchain-technologies/</guid>
      <description>Presentation and paper proceeding in the 4th Olympus International Conference on Supply Chains (14-15 September 2018, Katerini), on the topic &amp;ldquo;Traceability Decentralization in Supply Chain Management Using Blockchain Technologies&amp;rdquo;. Co-author Christos Sermpinis.
Abstract With the increase of web users and applications with real time requests, the ability to identify, track and trace elements of a product as it moves in the supply chain is deemed necessary, and for many industries is even mandated by national or international regulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic - PKI Decentralization Using Blockchain Technologies</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/pki-decentralization-using-blockchain-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/pki-decentralization-using-blockchain-technologies/</guid>
      <description>My masters thesis, supervised by Athena Vakali, was based on blockchain technologies with the title “PKI Decentralization Using Blockchain Technologies”.
Abstract The Public Key Infrastructure (PKI) is used widely on the Internet in order to certify the identity of users, and as a result encrypt the communication between two parties and make it more secure. From this model, multiple problems can arise, most of them due to its centralized nature. In the past, there have been cases of Certificate Authorities distributing rogue certificates that resulted in attacks, targeting users of the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks - Introduction to Bitcoin and Blockchain Technologies (Greek)</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/talks-introduction-to-bitcoin-and-blockchain-technologies-greek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/talks-introduction-to-bitcoin-and-blockchain-technologies-greek/</guid>
      <description>Presentation at the &amp;ldquo;Bitcoin and Machine Learning joint meetup&amp;rdquo; taking place at Thessaloniki.
Presentation Video
Slides
Meetup Link
Blog Post</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic - Integration of Near Field Communication into Warehouse Management Systems (BSc Thesis)</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/integration-of-near-field-communication-into-warehouse-management-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/integration-of-near-field-communication-into-warehouse-management-systems/</guid>
      <description>My bachelors thesis, supervised by Dimitrios Folinas, was based on NFC and WMS technologies with the title “Integration of Near Field Communication into Warehouse Management Systems”.
Abstract (Greek) Στην παρούσα εργασία θα αναφερθούμε και θα εξετάσουμε μία καινοτόμο εφαρμογή που έχει να κάνει με την εφαρμογή της τεχνολογίας NFC, και παράλληλα της πολιτικής BYOD, στα συστήματα WMS. Τα κύρια σημεία που εξετάστηκαν είναι το αν υπάρχει ενδιαφέρον από τους εργαζομένους, όσο αναφορά την εφαρμογή ενός τέτοιου συστήματος στον χώρο εργασίας τους, και αν είναι δυνατή η ανάπτυξη ενός ολοκληρωμένου συστήματος με την προσθήκη των τεχνολογιών και πολιτικών που προτείνονται.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic - Integration of Augmented Reality technology into Warehouse Management Systems</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/integration-of-augmented-reality-technology-into-warehouse-management-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/integration-of-augmented-reality-technology-into-warehouse-management-systems/</guid>
      <description>Presentation in the &amp;ldquo;12th Student Conference on Management Science and Technology&amp;rdquo; taking place in Athens on 14th of May 2015. The subject is my innovative idea on the &amp;ldquo;Integration of Augmented Reality technology into Warehouse Management Systems&amp;rdquo; based on my paper made in the context of my studies in the Technological Educational Institute of Central Macedonia.
Slides</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic - Integration of Near Field Communication technology into Warehouse Management Systems</title>
      <link>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/integration-of-near-field-communication-technology-into-warehouse-management-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 16:56:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cr0wtom.github.io/projects/integration-of-near-field-communication-technology-into-warehouse-management-systems/</guid>
      <description>Presentation in the &amp;ldquo;12th Student Conference on Management Science and Technology&amp;rdquo; taking place in Athens on 14th of May 2015. The subject is my innovative idea on the &amp;ldquo;Integration of Near Field Communication technology into Warehouse Management Systems&amp;rdquo; based on my paper made in the context of my studies in the Technological Educational Institute of Central Macedonia.
Slides</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
